{
    "subject": "resource/Sitmar_Cruises",
    "predicate": "ontology/regionServed",
    "object": "resource/Australasia",
    "human_readable": "Sitmar Cruises serves Australasia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9136171340942383,
            "question": "Are there any specific countries within Australasia that Sitmar Cruises focuses on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9096457958221436,
            "question": "How long has Sitmar Cruises been operating in Australasia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8713542819023132,
            "question": "Does Sitmar Cruises have any partnerships with other companies in Australasia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8167552947998047,
            "question": "Which continent is covered by Sitmar Cruises' service area?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7604709267616272,
            "question": "What region does Sitmar Cruises serve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6515821218490601,
            "question": "Where does Sitmar Cruises provide services?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6395076513290405,
            "question": "Can you name other cruise lines that serve Australasia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40712234377861023,
            "question": "What types of cruises does Sitmar Cruises offer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4016260802745819,
            "question": "What type of company is Sitmar Cruises?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20736739039421082,
            "question": "Is Australasia a region or country?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sitmar Cruises serves Australasia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7094_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of company is Sitmar Cruises?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7094_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What types of cruises does Sitmar Cruises offer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7094_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name other cruise lines that serve Australasia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7094_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7094_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7094_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7094_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7094_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7094_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7094_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7094_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7094_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7094_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7094_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple \"Sitmar Cruises serves Australasia\":\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while the documents mention that Sitmar Cruises operated cruises from North America and Europe to Australia, there is no evidence to suggest that they served other parts of Australasia (which includes New Zealand and nearby Pacific island nations) in addition to Australia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Sitmar Cruises operated services to and from Australasia, as evidenced by passages mentioning cruises originating from North America for Australian ports, operations between Europe and Australia until the early 1970s, and further activities like the MV Fairstar serving cruises leaving Sydney."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Sitmar Cruises' primary services were not confined to cruises from Australian ports, but rather originated from other than North American ports.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}